回顾课程第四节，我们学习了
Back in lesson four, we learned that the
Android Runtime(运行时)会杀掉那些activity处于不可见状态的app，
Android Runtime will kill apps with no visible activities,
来为前台的app释放需要的资源。
in order to free resources needed by the foreground
但要是你的程序中的一些任务需要在
app. But what if your app has tasks that
activity不可见的情况下继续执行肿么办，比如
need to continue when the activity isn't visible, things
下载文件，上传相片，或者听音乐呢？
like downloading files, uploading photos, or playing music? Well,
针对这个有一个专门的程序组件：Service(服务)。我们已经
there's an application component for that. Services. We've already
介绍了Activities,Content Providers,
introduced Activities, Content Providers,
Broadcast Reciviers 和intents。
Broadcast Receivers and Intents. Services,
Services是安卓应用组件整副拼图里的最后一块。
are the final piece to the Android app component
启动Service和启动activity类似
puzzle. You start services much like you do activities, by
通过调用startService方法，并向该方法传递一个intent对象。
passing in an intent to a Start Service call.
停止服务也是相同的方式，通过调用
And you can stop services the same way, by calling
stopService，并传递你想要停止的
Stop Service and passing in the name of the
服务的名字。不像activity，service没有
service you want to stop. Unlike activities, services have no
交互界面，且他们比后台进程有更高的
user interface and they run at a higher priority than
活动优先权。这意味着当系统资源不足的时候
background activities. This means that an app with a running
程序中的后台服务
service is less likely to be killed by the run
更容易被runtime(运行时)所保留
time, in order to free resources for the foreground activities.
事实上，默认情况下，系统会重启
In fact, by default, the system will attempt to restart
那些在程序终止他们之前被系统所终止的服务。
services that are terminated before they are stopped from within
在这个简化的生命周期里面可以看出来。
the app. This is reflected in this simplified life cycle.
和Activities相比,Services被设计来执行
Compared to Activities, Services are designed to execute longer running
那些需要长时间运行的任务。典型地，你只需要
tasks that shouldn't be interrupted. Typically, you'll only need to
重写onStartCommand，在这里添加你后台需要运行的任务代码
override the onStartCommand handler, which is where you begin the background
想要执行的后台程序。但要注意的是，
task you wish to execute. But notice that there are
没有监管状态改变的处理程序来反映
no handlers for monitoring changes in state, to reflect the
app移动到后台进程。这是因为
app moving to the background. This is because the running
running service 自身发送了一个信号到框架那
service itself sends a signal to the framework that the
控制app要考虑到要比那些
containing app should be considered higher priority than other apps
在后台没有运行服务的其他app有更高的优先权。在一些
in the background that don't have running services. In some
情况下，你的service可能会执行一个任务来使那些
cases your service may performing a task, that while not
没有UI，不能被中断的进程来干扰到用户体验。
having UI, can't be interrupted without interfering with the user experience.
例如，听音乐或者汽车导航的急救。
For example, playing music or helping with in car
在这些情形里，你能指明让你的
navigation. In these cases, you can indicate that your
server通过开启Foreground被运行在前台。
server should be considered to be running in the
你会发现这个通知里面包含了一个通告。
foreground by calling startForeground. You'll notice that this call takes
它会被展示且不会被
in a notification. This will be displayed, and can't
解散直到服务终止，或者你
be dismissed until the service has stopped, or you
呼叫终止Foreground。稍后你将会和
call stopForeground. You'll learn more about notifications a little
Dan学习更多关于通告的知识。但是现在，请记住
later, with Dan. But for now, note that a foreground
一个前台service和一个前台activity运行起来具有相同的优先权。
service runs at the same priority as a foreground
这使得run time不可能
activity. Making it nearly impossible for the run time
杀掉进程来释放资源。现在，你
to kill in order to free resources. Now, you
自己可能会想，我要解决掉大量
may be thinking to yourself, I could save a lot
处理生命周期的麻烦，仅仅通过创建
of trouble dealing with life cycles, just by creating
long running或者甚至foreground services。嗯，我是在
long running, or even foreground services. Well, I grew up
澳大利亚沿岸长大的，所以我很早
along the coast in Australia, so I learned young
就知道逆流游泳容易疲劳而且最终是徒劳的。
that swimming against the current is exhausting and ultimately futile.
在这个案例里，表明要使
In this case, that means making it more difficult
系统成功管理资源是很困难的，最终很易导致
for the system to manage resources, ultimately leading to a
一个坏的用户体验。要顺流游泳。使用前台
worse user experience. Swim with the current. Use foreground
服务只在有绝对需求的情况下，
services only when and for as long as absolutely necessary,
然后尽快终止所有的服务。
and stop all services as quickly as possible. It's
记录像activity和receivers，services
also important to note that like activities and receivers, services
运行在主要路径上是很重要的。所以你将需要
run on the main thread. So you'll need to
使用一个后台路径或者一个思考任务来执行
use a background thread or a think task to execute
你希望要使用的服务的long runningtasks。
the long running tasks you wish to do
为了使生活更简便一些，你可以
within your service. To make life easier, you can
使用指令服务类函数。
use the intent service class. Which implements the most
对于使用被执行在服务里的指令来说， 这是实施最普遍的最佳实践路径。
common best practice pattern, for usi  ng intents, which are
它创立了一个队列
executed within a service. It creates a queue of
来容纳即将进入的指令，当开启服务被唤醒的时候传递进来。
incoming intents, passed in when start service is called.
然后这些会在后台路径按次序的宣告进进程，
These are then, processed sequentially on a background thread,
包括onhandleintent处理程序，和你的指令服务实施。
within the onHandleIntent handler, within your intent service implementation.
当队列是空的时候，服务器自己会终止
When the queue is empty the service self terminates
直到收到一个新的指令和进程再次开始。
until a new intent is received and the process begins
services是一个很有用的工具，然后理解
again. Services are a powerful tool and it's important
你能怎样使用他们是很重要的但在实践中
to understand how you can use them but in practice
经常有一个框架替代来转换你的
there's often a framework alternative to rolling your own
服务实施。你将会在后续的课程中学习到
service implementation. Whether that be an intent service for executing
关于是否执行后台任务和同步适配器。
background tasks or the sync adapter which you'll learn about
完美运行后台数据同步。
later in this lesson. Perfect for performing background data synchronization